[{"answer": "Well, I think it's incredibly shameful, but I think you're hitting on the things that I don't think he can ever take back, which is he went through the lengths, not simply of lying, but the litigiousness of suing the \"London Times\" for defamation, very expensive, winning a $500,000 judgment.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "It's a pretty shameful moment, isn't it, for him?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I've read that they might consider reinstating him in eight years.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "I don't see any way that he can do that, do you?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Given the scale of his betrayal to you personally, will you ever talk to him again?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Let me -- let me update you as they're coming to this now.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "But why would I ever believe anything he says to me or anyone?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, if he thought the climb up the Pyrenees was difficult, he's going to find the climb to regain his reputation is even worse.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Is there any way back for Lance Armstrong?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Yes or no, did you ever take banned substances to enhance your cycling performance?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Yes or no, was one of those banned substances EPO?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Did you ever blood dope or use blood transfusions to enhance your cycling performance?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Did you ever use any other banned substances like testosterone, cortisone, or human growth hormone?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Yes or no, in all seven of your Tour de France victories, did you ever take banned substances or blood dope?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Not in my opinion.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Seven times in a row?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "We're done with the yes and nos.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "We're done with the yes and nos?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "For me or for --", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Began when?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Mid-'90s.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "For you?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "No, he's it.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "I mean, Christine, is -- in the Pantheon of sporting cheats, has anybody come close to Lance Armstrong?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Absolutely, Piers.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "His lawyers have allowed him to do this, but just hearing those ramifications, knowing what I do about the lawsuits against British newspapers and so on, surely, he's going to be facing a battery of lawsuits, isn't he?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Well, it's not quite that simple.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Could he go to jail for perjury, for any of these confessions now?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "I feel bad for him.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "What do you feel for Lance Armstrong tonight on that level?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Well, what you have publicly displayed in this instance, is you aren't as good as you think you are and you're not as good as you act.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "What was the sort of overriding thing you learned about yourself that perhaps made you a better man?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, that's up for each individual to decide.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Do you expect widespread forgiveness?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "A buddy of mine from down in Beaufort I think summed it incredibly really well.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "What do you see is missing that perhaps you can fill in terms of a gap?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Well, Mark Sanford, I wish you all the very best.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "And so what I want to do is take what I've learned and hopefully apply it to again a great conundrum that now exists in Washington, which is how do we get our financial house in order?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Well, listen, I think the NRA is in a fundamentally different position than they were just 35 days ago.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "What do we do about that?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Yes, you know, I have talked to so many of these parents and families over the last few weeks.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Who's going to show some kind of political leadership?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Piers, thank you very much for having me on.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "Mr. Elder, no gun problem in America?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Yes, it's a claim.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Claim?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Piers, this has been studied many times by organizations like the Heritage Foundation.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "So how do you explain that using your argument?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "There are lots of factors why people commit crimes.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "How do you explain it's not happening in New York?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "LDER: They most certainly are.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "These are things you should consider, aren't they, before you dismiss there being no gun problem?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "This is a Mardi Gras king cake that was sent by Ms. Romak (ph) from New Orleans.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "What is this?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "I think it's been so the right path for you.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "So, I mean, look, I straddle the line and sometimes I -- you can't help but wonder, is this the right path or is this the right path?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "I don't like -- this is my personal opinion.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "When you hear this debate -- it's an interesting debate, I think, about whether you should have armed security in school, what do you think?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "I'm very, very frustrated with this story.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "I think Lance Armstrong will go down in history as the greatest sporting cheat of them all.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "Look, I know how much need there is for money and for research and for things for cancer.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "As a survivor, can you divorce what he has done as a survivor to help cancer and other charities, and the money he has raised, from everything we now know about him?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "I think there can be.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Is there such a thing as bad money when it comes to fundraising for charity?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "It's depressing.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "How are you dealing with no alcohol?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "Calm everyone down a bit, you know.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "I thought it was a lot of people were in a funk, you know, whether it's tragedies around the world or close to home.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "Why did you come up with the idea?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "He's just become a grandfather.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "I think Charlie probably feels pretty damn relieved he made it to be a grandfather.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "Look, I think that it's one of those things that you wonder who is going to be wearing the bib at the end, the grandchild or Charlie Sheen?", "qSentId": 709}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130117pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "Is that always the demon on your shoulder?", "qSentId": 729}]